Sara-Jane Gibbs

UX Designer

Profile

I am a UX designer who aspires to create engaging products that ultimately help people in their day to day life.

My experience includes 7 years working in digital production for Arcadia Group, here I worked directly on the delivery of digital products for Evans, working closely with designers, web developers and stakeholders. My most recent role has been at Fin-Tech company, ICX4, where I was part of a team redesigning the way customer data is displayed to banks.

Experience

UX Designer

ICX4 / July 2017 - December 2017

ICX4 work with leading banks to ensure that they have access to current and relevant customer data.

Key Responsibilities:

- Ownership of a project, designing wireframes for data profiles based on use cases (KYC, On-boarding, Compliance, AML).
- Worked closely with the User Researcher, ensuring designs fit the users needs, through testing with users, creating user journeys and verifying designs against use cases.
- Worked closely with the Visual Designer to ensure they were aware with design decisions when wireframes were handed over.
- Attended Client meetings to show work in progress and gain feedback from them.
- Led design workshops to gain ideas on how data could be presented.

UXDI Teaching Assistant

General Assembly / June 2017 - July 2017

Having completed the User Experience Immersive course, I was asked to be a teaching assistant on one of the courses. Here, I was able to offer valuable support and advice to the students, deliver feedback on their projects, as well as support the course tutor.

UX Designer

O2 World Chat / May 2017

Working in a team, our goal was to redesign how users discover and engage with the sharing functionality within the iOS app. In a two week sprint, we focused on user research, heuristic analysis, information architecture, creating wireframes, prototyping, testing and iterating our designs. We were then able to deliver high-fidelity designs, a revised site map and final stakeholder presentation.

Contact

London

07837950449

sarajanegibbs@gmail.com

sarajanegibbs.co.uk

linkedin.com/in/sarajanegibbs

Key Skills

User Research

User Flows

User Journeys

Task Analysis

Affinity Map

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Interaction Design

Usability Testing

Presentations

Agile Methodologies

Teamwork

Self Motivation

Communication

Software

Sketch

Omnigraffle

Marvel

Invision

JIRA

Photoshop

HTML & CSS

Keynote

Sara-Jane Gibbs

UX Designer

UX Designer

Generation Success / April 2017

Working in a team, in a two week sprint, our goal was to redesign Generation Success' website. In this sprint, through user research, information architecture, wireframing, prototyping and testing we produced a high-fidelity responsive website design, design specification, final stakeholder presentation and wider site recommendations.

UX Designer

General Assembly / February 2017 - April 2017

A 10 week, full time immersive course learning and practising the UX design process. Throughout the course I worked on projects which covered user research, interaction and interface design, prototyping and testing, and working with clients.

Projects:

Science Museum App:

Delivery of high-fidelity wireframes for an app that enhances the visitors experience. Working in a team of four, in a two week sprint, through user research, sketching and wireframing, prototyping and testing, we produced an engaging app that allows visitors to plan their visit and navigate around the museum with use of an interactive map.

Ecommerce Website:

Delivery of desktop wireframes for a new ecommerce website. Working individually, I produced wireframes for a product list page, product detail page and checkout flow.

Online Production Coordinator

Evans - Arcadia / May 2014 - February 2017

Key Responsibilities:

- Coordinated daily CMS builds of website content on desktop, mobile and apps.
- Management of two Production Assistants; responsible for their training and development.
- Worked closely with marketing and design teams to ensure that content was delivered on time.
- Along with Production Manager, helped develop website.
- Worked closely with website development team to implement new site functionality.
- Worked with third parties to carry out Multivariate and A/B Testing

Key Achievements:

- Managed the implementation and launch of a new mobile platform for Evans. Working closely with development teams and Project Managers.
- Managed the relaunch of the desktop website, transferring data from one programme to another and thoroughly testing the customer experience.

Education

UXDI Course

General Assembly / February -April 2017

B.A Media Studies

De Montfort University / 2007 - 2010

Interests

Exploring new countries and trying new and exciting food.

I love music and finding new artists to listen to, when I hear an album I really like, I'll play it on repeat for weeks.

Looking through cookbooks and trying new recipes.

Exploring London. I have lived here all my life, but there is constantly more and more to see and do. It is such a great city to live in.